<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SistelGroup</string>
    <string name="Company">00000000</string>
    <string name="Name">Name</string>
    <string name="Surname">Surname</string>
    <string name="dni">NIE</string>
    <string name="checkin">Register</string>
    <string name="whosvisiting">Who is visiting?</string>
    <string name="motiu">Visit Reason</string>
    <string name="Success">Successful register</string>
    <string name="idioma_canviat">Language changed correctly</string>
    <string name="URLerror">URL incorrecta</string>
    <string name="NameCompany">Company name</string>
    <string name="hello">Hola</string>
    <string name="external_dir">GetSignature</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="sign">Sign</string>
    <string name="RGPD">Accepto les polítiques de l\'empresa</string>
    <string name="RGPDTitle">CONFIDENTIALITY AND LOYALTY PACT</string>
    <string name="RGPDMessage1">Confidentiality pact between</string>
    <string name="RGPDMessage">and present collaborator visitor.\n \nThe collaborator declares to know and accept that the reason of the services provided in the company will have access to confidential information and documentation (that will be marked as such and other occasions not and may even transmit some information verbally.)\n\nThe collaborator also declares to know and accept that in the sector in which the company develops its activities, maintaining the confidentiality of such information and documentation is an essential element, and that, therefore, not respecting said confidentiality causes a serious prejudice to the company with possible legal claims for breach of contracts signed with clients.\n\nFor all this, the collaborator is obligated in front of the company to:\n\n\n1.	Confidential information\n\nMaintain in the strictest confidentiality and not disclose, disseminate, publish or use, for purposes unrelated to the company, the information of a technical, commercial, strategic, financial or any other type that is provided by the company or that may have access in any way because of its provision of services in it.\n\nThe information referred to above includes the following types of information, (whether in writing or not), without which the present enumeration excludes other kinds of information also confidential.\n\nComputers  programs, databases, market research, research and development, ideas, inventions, concepts, designs, drawings, organizational charts, processes, procedures, “know-how”, formulas, data, programs of any kind, improvements, discoveries, materials and techniques marketing, research and development plans, new products, customer names, marketing channels and trade secrets and any other information related to customers and suppliers, price lists, pricing policies, sales policy, financial information, budgets, templates, methods of management and accounting, commercial alliances, agreements with third parties and business projects.\n\nThe obligation described in this section shall apply both to the company’s own information or classified as confidential information whether it is owned by the company or not, or has been developed by the company or not, as well as that information that has been provided by companies or entities integrated in the same group or by third parties (including customers, suppliers, distributors and collaborating companies).\n\nThe collaborator will adopt all the necessary measures to guarantee the confidentiality of such information, an obligation that will maintain its full effectiveness and validity once this labor relationship has been completed in accordance with the provisions of section 2 below.\n\n\n2.	Confidentiality pact \n\nKeep indefinitely the obligation of confidentiality provided for in the previous paragraphs, both during the validity of your employment relationship with the company and once completed the same for any cause, even for dismissal, although the same would be declared improcedent.\n\nThe collaborator must obtain the prior authorization of the company for the realization of any presentation, report and other publications, to the extent that these correspond to the sector of activity of the company or may affect their interests.\n\n\n3. Industrial and intellectual property rights\n\nThe collaborator acknowledges and accepts that all the data, knowledge of any kind placed at his disposal, reference materials, annotations, databases, computer programs, diagrams, drawings, memoranda, documentation or recordings, or any kind of form, and support, that incorporate or reflect any kind of confidential information are company’s property.\n\nThe collaborator agrees to return to the company if requested and at any time, all copies of said materials and any physical support that are under their control.\n\nFinally, the collaborator undertakes and compromise to adopt the necessary measures to protect the industrial and intellectual property rights that always have registered or can register the company and the rest of companies in your group.\n\n\n4.	Retourn of information \n\nFacilitate the return to the company, by terminating or ending the provision of services, all information, inventions, formulas, secrets, methods, or discoveries and, in general, documentation relating to the activities of the company, that you have used during your relationship work with it.\n\n\n5.	Collaboration \n\nCollaborate and assist the company in its defense against any infringement of its intellectual, industrial property rights or any breach of its business secrets. This commitment will also involve the obligation to duly inform the company in case the employee has knowledge that such infringement or violation has occurred or is occurring.\n\n\n6.	Loyalty pact\n \nIn accordance with the law 3/1991 of January 10, in force , of March 29, 2014, of unfair competition and article 5 of Royal Legislative Decree 1/1995, of March 24, which approves the text of consolidated the law of the statute of the workers, while the collaborator provides services in the company, the collaborator will not carry out any labor activity, either on behalf of another person, on their own account or by an interposed person, for companies that investigate, manufacture and/or market the same products or services and go to the same circle of potential customers  that make in danger  the interests of the company.\n\nLikewise, it will be considered disloyal in accordance with the reference law:\n•	The disclosure or exploitation, without authorization of the company, of industrial secrets or any other confidential information to which it has had legitimate access but with the duty to reserve or illegitimately.\n•	The induction to other workers and/or collaborators so that they violate their duties in the matter of confidentiality and non-concurrence with the company.\n•	The induction to other workers and/or collaborators to solve their contract of employment in to order to benefit from the industrial or business secrets of the company.\n\n\n7.	Personal data protection\n\nThe development and execution of the functions of the collaborator does not involve access to confidential information that implies access to personal data, but in the case that by reason of the development of the work contract such access should occur, declare that access will be carried out in the terms of March 6, 2011, and are obligated  to adopt as many security measures as are mandatory in order to avoid the alteration, access or improper use of the data to which each party has access.\n\n\n8.	Applicable law \n\nThis agreement will be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the Spanish legislation applicable to the effect.\n\n\n9.	 Consequences of non-compliance \n\nExcept in those cases in which it has been expressly authorized by the company, the breach of the aforementioned obligations will entail the following responsibilities for the employee:\n\na)	Disciplinary labor responsibility: cessation of the contract for the provision of services.\nb)	A contractual liability for the damages caused (arts.1.101 and following of the civil code).\nc)	Criminal liability: crimes of discovery or disclosure of business secrets (articles 278 and 279 of the criminal code).\n\nIn addition to these responsibilities, the company may take legal action for compensation arising from the provisions of the law of patents, trademarks, and industrial designs as well as the law of unfair competition or any other that results from application.\n\n\n10.	Acceptance and compression\n\nThe collaborator assumes the commitments established in the previous agreements on industrial property rights, intellectual property, confidentiality pact and loyalty pact.\nThe collaborator declares that the content and scope of this document has been extensive and sufficiently explained by the company, as well as the consequences that the breach of the same would entail, for which it declares to understand its meaning and scope, accepting it expressly.</string>
    <string name="Accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="Decline">Decline</string>
    <string name="Rellenar">I accept company policies</string>
    <string-array name="List_CompanyVisited">
        <item>SistelGroup</item>
        <item>S.A. Sistel</item>
        <item>DigiProces S.A.</item>
        <item>6TL Engineering</item>
        <item>SmartLift S.L.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="List_Visited">
        <item>Gerard</item>
        <item>Xavi</item>
        <item>David</item>
        <item>Roger</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
